Hello friends, welcome to today's
new video. Friends, in today's video,
we are going to talk about how we can download the
PDF of any of our insurance policies.
Friends, if you have any type of vehicle,
whether you have a car, a bike, a bus, a
truck, or anything else, and your
insurance policy is lost, lost,
damaged, or you want to download its PDF, then
friends, you can download the PDF
of its insurance policy only by the vehicle number.
Or friends, if
you want to download the PDF of any other type of insurance,
like if we have
health insurance, live stream
insurance, LIC insurance, then you
can download its PDF too,
but to download it, you must have the
policy number. But friends,
if you want to download the PDF
of any insurance,
you can download it only by the vehicle number. So, for this, first of all, you have to go to the
official website of Parivahan Seva. I will
give you the link for this in the description. I have
come to this website because from here
we will first get the policy number, only then we
can download the policy video. So, after getting the
policy number,  For this, if you
get an option here,
you have to go to Information Service and
click on the option Details here. After clicking on this,
friends, you will
get the option to enter the mobile number here, but you have to
click on Create Account.
After clicking on Create Account, friends, you have to
enter the mobile number and email ID here.
Click on Generate OTP, then
an OTP will be sent to your mobile number.
You have to verify it by entering the OTP. After that, friends,
you will get the option to create a password.
Whatever password you want to create,
you can create it here. Once you
create the password, friends, your account will be created.
After the account is created, friends, you will
come back here. Here you will enter your mobile number.
After entering the mobile number,
click on Next. After clicking on Next,
friends, whatever password you have created,
enter that password here. Then click on Continue.
After clicking on Continue, friends, you will get the option of Status from here.
Here you have to enter the
vehicle number of the vehicle for which you want to download the insurance policy.
After entering the vehicle number, this
capsule will be shown. Fill this capsule here.  We have to
search and click,
but
we need the policy number here, so
you can see here, our policy number is given
below, but we have also given the policy number of which company we have taken for
our vehicle, till
when is your policy validity, that is also given here,
what we have to do is copy the policy
number shown here,
after getting the policy number, friends, to download the PDF of the insurance policy,
we will have to
download the DJ Roar application in our mobile
or friends, you
can go to the website by going digital in Google, like I have
opened the website of Busy Logon here, I have logged in my account here,
so after logging in,
friends, whatever documents you
download, all of them
go to your issue documents here and whatever
document you want to download, you can also download
them here by clicking search here, here
below if you
can also see your profile, whatever your
details are, they will be given here, to
download the policy, I searched and
click on the comments section,
after clicking on the search document section
Friends, many documents are uploaded here.
Whatever you want to download,
whatever document you
download from the website, friends, you keep it here.
These are valid all over India. So, to
download the insurance policy here, we will write the name of the company.
Whichever company's insurance
policy you have, we will write the benefits of that company here.
I wrote that it is from Cholamandalam,
so I wrote Chola here, so Chola
means all the insurances are uploaded here.
Now you can see that Cholamandalam has
health insurance here,
tax insurance is also uploaded.
If you ask friends, that is also uploaded.
Commercial vehicle means the yellow plate
number plates like bus, truck, etc.,
all of them are uploaded here.
We are uploading two wheeler
insurance, so I will click on this section.
If you have health insurance
and you have the policy number, then
you can download that here too. I say
click on two wheeler from easy here.
After clicking on the two wheeler section,
friends, your date of birth is 100%.  The birth has automatically appeared here,
what we have to do is
enter the police number which we have taken out from there,
we will fill that number here,
after entering the number, friends, you
will click on get document, after clicking on head document,
friends, your request will be submitted
and within 1 minute, friends,
your document will be issued and here
you will be added in the issued document, now you
can see our document successfully
and here our document has been added and
friends, with this you can download any insurance policy, it is
not necessary that the
ID has been created in your name, so you download only your
insurance policy, you
can download anyone's insurance policy,
you can see friends, our
insurance policy has been added here, it is
written Insurance Policy Two Wheeler, the
policy number has been added here and the
date when it was added has also been added here,
23 November 2022, which is today's date,
that time is also showing here, now to
download the policy, friends,
you will click on it here
in the download section, friends, here you will
get the option to download PDF, click
Friends, you can save
your video anywhere on your mobile or computer.
I will download it here and
show it to you. Friends,
after downloading, your PDF will be available to view in this manner. So
friends, in this way you
can easily download the PDF of any of your vehicles, that too only
with the vehicle number. I hope friends, you must have
liked this video. If you
liked the video, then like it and if you are new to the channel, then
definitely subscribe to the channel.
Thank you very much friends for watching the video.